Hello,
hello friends, welcome to back stocks.
Friends, a good update is coming. A
little
while ago, a notice has been filed by ICICI Lombard.
In that notice, the
company has declared a change in its quarterly result date. Along with this,
this time the
company can also give a different date. So let's
quickly go over this notice and understand
what is written in it. So
friends, we have come to that note. You
can see here that
a board meeting has been scheduled by the board of directors of the company, which means that on the
same
day the company's shares will be sold. This means that
this time the quarterly result of the company is going to
come on April 21st. So this is a
very good thing because
every investor, every shareholder waits for this date.
Now pay attention to one more thing here. The
company is
also making arrangements for a switch for its shareholders.
You can see here. Yes friends,
dividend, but on April 21st there will be a board
meeting first, the vote will be approved, then
their  Share holders will get the button,
so you can say that here we are getting a very
good news for the
shareholders of ICICI Lombard.
Now it remains to be seen what the result of this U for will be.
If the result is good
then it will be icing on the cake. So
friends, that's all for now. If you are
new to the channel then keep subscribing to this channel
because on this channel we keep
bringing updates related to the share market.
So we will meet in the next video. Till then
goodbye.